Okay,here's his diaper bag...
这是他的尿布袋…
...and his Mr. Winky.
…跟他的眨眼先生
And...
还有…
... him. Hi!
…他，嗨！
-How did everything go? -Great!
一切都还好吗？ 好，很好
There was a projectile...
我们有个喷射性…
...throwing up incident, but he started it.
…呕吐事件，是他先开始的
We've gotta go.
我们得走了
Oh,right.
对了
I've got some news. It's about us.
我有个消息，是关于我们的
You and me?
你跟我？
No. Susan and me.
不，苏珊跟我
The other "us."
另一个“我们”
We're getting married.
我们要结婚了
As in,"I now pronounce you wife and wife" married?
就像“现在宣布 你们为妻子跟妻子”
We'd like you to come. We understand if you don't want to.
我们欢迎你来，若你不想来 我们也完全了解
Why wouldn't I want to come? I had fun at the first wedding.
我为什么会不想去呢？ 第一次婚礼我很开心
I just thought that
我想也许…
Why shouldn't I be happy for you? What would it say about me...
不…我是说… 我为什么不该替你高兴呢？
...if I couldn't revel in your joy?
…如果我不能 为你的快乐而快乐
And I'm reveling,baby! Believe me!
那我算什么呢？ 我说的是真的，相信我
Is your finger caught in that chair?
你的手指被椅子夹住了吗？
Want us to go?
你要我们离开吗？
The One With the Lesbian Wedding
-=BT之家DRM小组 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 河马压缩制作 本字幕为河马根据R3DVD OCR得来
-=BT之家DRM小组 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 六人行 第2季 第11集 同志婚礼
This is cool. You're actually on television.
好酷耶 你真的要在电视上出现了
I know. It really hit me last night.
我知道 我昨晚才真正的意识到
I'm on Days of our Lives.
我要在 “我们的日子”里面演出了
Then I started thinking about us, and how these are the days of our lives.
然后我开始想我们的事 我发现这正是“我们的日子”
Yes!
帅
What?
怎么了？
Carol and Susan's caterer had a bike accident...
帮凯洛跟苏珊办喜酒的人 这个周末骑登山车出了车祸…
...and she's in a full-body cast.
…全身都上了石膏
They asked me,which is cool since I've never catered...
他们要我办，这真太酷了吧 我从来没有搞过这个…
...and I need the money. Is this a problem?
…而且我很需要钱 这对你不会构成问题吧？
-Would it matter? -You're so great!
那有关系吗？ 你太棒了
Thank you!
谢谢
-You're really not going? -I'm really not.
你真的不去吗？ 我当然真的不去
They already live together. Why do they need to get married?
我不懂她们已经住在一起了 为什么还需要结婚？
They love each other.
因为她们相爱啊
They wanna celebrate that love with the people close to them.
她们要跟她们亲密的人 一起庆祝那份爱
If you wanna call that a reason.
如果你硬要说那个理由的话
Who's the bitterest man in the living room?
谁是客厅里最苦的人？
The bitterest man in the living room?
客厅里最苦的男人？
Hi,neighbor.
嗨，芳邻
-I thought you were over this. -That has nothing to do with it.
罗斯，我以为你不在意了 那跟这个没有关系
If she were marrying a guy, you wouldn't expect me to go.
她要是嫁了一个男的话 没有人会觉得我应该去
If she were marrying a guy, she'd be the worst lesbian ever.
他要是嫁了个男的话 那不是史上最烂的同性恋了
Did I miss it?
我错过了吗？
No,I'm on right after this guy shoots himself.
还没有，这个砘镒陨敝后 我就上阵了
She's pretty.
她很漂亮耶
And she's really nice.
对了，她人也很好
She taught me about how to work with the cameras...
她教我怎么样在镜头前演戏…
...and smell-the-fart acting.
…还有“闻屁味”演戏法
-I'm sorry,what? -Excuse me?
对不起？ 什么？
You got so many lines to learn so fast that sometimes...
在短时间之内 要记那么多的台词…
...you need a minute to remember your next one.
…有时候你需要时间想下一句
So while you're thinking...
所以当你想的时候呢…
...you take this big pause where you look all intense.
…你停顿一下 表情装得非常的凝重
Like this....
像这样…
Here's my scene! Here's my scene!
轮到我了，我来了
Mrs. Wallace?
华太太？
Dr. Drake Ramoray, your sister's neurosurgeon.
我是雷医生 令妹的神经外科医师
Is she going to be all right?
告诉我，她会不会好起来？
I'm afraid the situation is much more dire than we'd expected.
恐怕令妹的情形 比我们想像的还要糟糕
Your sister's suffering from a...
令妹得的病是…
...subcranial hematoma.
…脑下血肿
Perhaps we can discuss this further over coffee.
或许我们可以 边喝咖啡边聊一下
Nice!
帅
For a minute,I thought you were actually smelling something.
刚有那么一会儿，我还真以为 你闻到了什么东西呢
-Do it again! -All right!
再来一次，演得太棒了 好…
-That was so good! -Do it again.
"Damn it,Braverman! It's right there on the chart!"
“该死，贝弗曼 就在那张图表上”
I gotta get to work. I got a big dinosaur bone to inspect.
太棒了，好了，我要去上班了 我有根大恐龙骨头要检查
No,that's me.
不…那是我
Oh,right.
对…你
Oh,thanks. Couldn't....
谢了，我没办法…
Is everything okay?
你还好吧？
No.
不
One of my clients died on the massage table today.
今天我有一个客人 死在按摩桌上
Oh,my God!
天啊
That's a little more relaxed than you want them to get.
你未免令他太放松了吧
She was,you know, 82 years old...
她已经八十二岁了…
...and her name was Mrs. Adelman.
…她叫艾德曼太太
Oh,honey.
甜心
It's just so strange. You know...
对呀，感觉怪怪的…
...she probably woke up this morning and thought...
…她早上醒来时说不定在想…
... I'll have some breakfast, take a walk,then have my massage.
…我去吃点早餐，然后去散步 然后，再去按个小摩
Little did she know God thought, "Okay,but that's it."
没有想到神在想 “好，但是就这样好了”
Oh,but the weirdest things was...
最诡异的事情是…
... I was cleansing her aura when it happened.
…发生的时候 我正在清她的灵气
And when her spirit left her body...
当她的灵魂离开身体的时候…
... I don't think it went very far.
…我不认为它走远了
What do you mean?
什么意思啊？
I think it went into me.
我想它上了我的身
This is so hard.
这太难了
I can't decide between lamb or duck.
我没有办法决定做羊还是鸭肉
Well,lambs are scarier.
当然了，羊肉比较恐怖
Or the movie would've been called Silence of the Ducks.
不然“那部电影”就会改为 “沉默的鸭子”了
Okay,who ordered what?
好了，谁点了什么？
I had the half-drunk cappuccino with the lipstick on the rim.
我相信我点了喝了一半 上面还有唇印的泡沫咖啡
And this with the cigarette butt in it,is that decaf?
对了，而这杯有烟屁股的 是无咖啡因的吗？
Oh,God.
天哪
You're so uptight about your mom coming.
真不敢相信 你妈要来会把你搞成这个样子
I know. I just don't want her to think that because...
我知道，只是这是她第一次来 我不想她觉得…
... I didn't marry Barry my life is crap.
…因为我没嫁给贝利 我的生活就完全是垃圾
Talk about crap,just listen to Stella Neidman...
说到垃圾 你不妨去试试听史黛拉…
...tell her story about Rod Steiger for the hundredth time.
…讲她跟施洛德的 老掉牙的故事
Pheebs? How long do you think this lady will be with us?
菲比？ 你想她会跟我们在一起多久？
I don't know. She obviously has some unfinished business.
我不知道，老太太显然 还有什么心愿还没完成呢
Sit up!
坐好
There she is!
乖女儿
-Mom! -Hey,sweetie!
妈 心肝
So this is where you work!
这就是你的公司啊
Oh,it's wonderful!
好棒啊
Is it a living room? Is it a restaurant? Who can tell?
这是客厅吗？还是餐厅？ 谁看得出来？
I guess that's the fun.
我猜乐趣就在那儿吧
Pretty much. Here,meet my friends.
差不多啦，来，看看我的朋友
Monica! You look gorgeous!
摩妮卡，你看起来好美哟
Oh,my! The last time I saw you, it was eat or be eaten.
上回我看到你的时候 是在吃或是被吃呢？
This is Joey.
这是乔伊
This is Phoebe.
这是菲比
This is Chandler.
这是钱德
You remember Ross?
你记得罗斯吧？
Oh,hello,Ross.
你好，罗斯
Mrs. Greene.
林太太
What do you think of my daughter,in the apron...
你们认为我系着围裙…妈呀
...with the big job!
…做大事的女儿怎么样？
Oh,Mom!
妈！
If you didn't pour the coffee, no one would have anything to drink.
没有你来倒咖啡呢 大家都休想喝到东西了
Believe me,sometimes that happens.
相信我，有时候真的会这样的
This is just so exciting! You know,I never worked.
太令人兴奋了 我从来没有做过事情
I went from my father's house to the sorority house...
我从我爸家 直接到大学妹妹会之家…
...to my husband's house. I am just so proud of you!
…然后再到我先生的家 我以你为荣，乖女儿
Really?
真的啊？
I know who you remind me of.
我知道你让我想起了谁了
Evelyn Durmer.
杜艾琳
That's before the lousy face-lift. Now she looks like Soupy Sales.
是去做蹩脚的拉皮手术前的她 现在她像苏比赛尔了
Pheebs? Who's Evelyn Durmer?
菲菲，杜艾琳是谁？
I don't know. Who's Soupy Sales?
不知道，苏比赛尔是谁啊？
Oh,my God!
老天啊
There's an unattractive nude man playing the cello.
有个丑陋的裸体男人 在拉大提琴
Just be glad he's not playing a smaller instrument.
是啊，还好他不是 在拉一个比较小的乐器
You have some life here,sweetie!
你的生活真有意思
Mom,I realize you were upset when I didn't marry Barry...
妈，我知道你跟爸 很不高兴我没有嫁给贝利…
...and get the house in the suburbs with all the security.
…住在郊外的大房子 过着不用担心柴米油盐的生活
This is just so much better for me.
可是，这样对我好多了
I know. You didn't love Barry,honey.
我知道，你不爱贝利，亲爱的
And I've never seen you this happy.
我也没见过你这么快乐过
I look at you and I think, "This is what I want."
看着你，我心里在想… “这是我要的”
For me.
这是为我吗？
Well,not just for you.
不只是为了你啦
What do you mean?
你是什么意思啊？
I'm considering leaving your father.
我在考虑离开你爸爸
All right,tell me if this is too cute.
好，告诉我这太可爱了
Lesbian wedding... chicken breasts.
同性恋婚礼…，鸡胸肉
Oh,God. I think I'm gonna be sick.
天啊，我想我快吐了
What? It's not like I'm putting little nipples on them.
什么？ 我又没有在上面放小乳头
-You had no idea? -None.
你完全不知道他们处得不好 不知道
They didn't fight?
他们不常吵架？
No,they didn't even talk to each other.
不，他们连话都不讲了
How was I suppose to know they were having problems?
天啊，我怎么会知道 他们之间有问题啊
You know,in my day, divorce was not an option.
在我那个时代 离婚不是个选择
Hey,look who's up!
看谁醒了
I just can't believe this is happening!
我只是无法相信这个事情嘛
When I was little, all parents got divorced.
我是说我小时候 每个人的父母都在闹离婚
I figured as an adult, I wouldn't have to worry about it.
我只是想，我长大了 就不用再担心这个了
Can't you look at this as flattering?
你可不可能 把这件事视为恭维呢？
She just wants to be like you.
我是说 她这样做是想向你学习
Well,couldn't she have just copied my haircut?
那她不能 学我的发型就好了吗？
When my parents divorced, they sent me to a shrink...
我父母离婚的时候 他们还叫我去看心理医生呢…
...and she told me that kids blame themselves.
…他们告诉我 所有的小孩都会怪自己
But in your case, it's actually kind of true.
就你而言，这真应该怪你呢
Oh,that's him.
就是他
Damn! My mail-order grandfather hasn't come yet.
该死，我邮购的爷爷还没寄来
-Phoebe? -Hi,Mr. Adelman.
菲比？ 是，艾先生
-Nice to see you. -Thanks for coming.
幸会，幸会 谢谢你来见我
That's okay. Although you did cut into my busy day of sitting.
没问题，不过你的确打扰了我 忙碌昏坐的一天
Do you wanna sit?
你要坐下来吗？
No,I spent most of my morning trying to stand up.
不…不用了 我早上花了好多时间才站起来
What can I do for you,my dear?
我能为你做些什么，亲爱的？
Okay,I don't know how to say this,but....
我不知道该怎么说啦…
I think when your wife's spirit left her body...
当你太太的灵魂 离开她身体的时候…
...it kind of stuck around...
…她转入了我的…
...in me.
…身上
You're saying my wife is in you?
你说我太太在你身上？
Yeah. You don't have to believe me,but...
你用不着相信我啦…
...can you think of any unfinished business she had?
…不过你能想出她或许 有什么未完成的心愿吗？
Any reason to hang around?
有什么原因让她留下来吗？
I don't know what to say.
我不知道该说什么
All I can think of is that...
我唯一能够想到的是…
...she used to say that before she died, she wanted to see everything.
…以前她常说她死之前 她想见识一切
-Everything? -Everything.
一切？ 一切
That's a lot of stuff.
那可真是不少
Oh,wait,l....
等一等…
I remember she also said she wanted to sleep with me one last time.
我想起来了，她还说 她想最后再跟我上一次床
I'm sorry. There's laughing in my head.
对不起，我脑袋里有笑声
Worth a shot,huh?
值得一试嘛
Look at this!
看这一张
These are all Halloween, three years ago.
这是三年前万圣节的照片
Oh,and look,here's Barry.
你看，这是贝利
He came straight from the office?
他直接从诊所过来吗？
Oh,no. That was his costume.
不，那是他的服装
See,he's actually an orthodontist, but he came as a regular dentist.
他是个牙齿矫正师 但他打扮成一般的牙医
You guys?
各位
Remember when I said that I don't need your help?
记得我以前说 谢了，我不需要你们帮忙？
Actually,I think you said...
事实上，我想你说的是…
... "Don't touch that and get out of my kitchen."
…“别乱碰 离我的厨房远一点”
Really? Weird. Anyway....
真的？奇怪，不过…
I planned really well. I planned and planned.
我一切都计划得很好 我计划计划又计划
I just didn't plan enough time to do it.
只是我想 我实际烹饪的时间计划得不够
-You want some help? -lf you want.
摩妮卡，需要帮忙吗？ 你要的话
What a day!
好长的一天
I took her everywhere.
我带这位老太太到处去逛
The Museum of Modern Art, Rockefeller Center...
我们去了现代美术馆 洛克裴勒中心…
...the Statue of Liberty.
…自由女神像
She's still with you?
她还跟着你啊？
Yes. I guess she hasn't seen everything yet.
对呀，我猜这位老太太 还没见过一切呢
Be right back. She has to go to the bathroom again.
我马上回来 她必须再去一趟厕所
Such a pretty face!
一张好漂亮的脸
Oh,this is so much fun! Just the girls!
这好好玩，就只有我们女生
Do you know what we should do? Does anybody have any marijuana?
知道我们该做什么吗？ 我想请问一下，谁有大麻？
God!
天啊
Look,no one's smoking pot around all this food.
听着 不准在这堆食物旁边吸大麻
Well,that's fine.
没关系
I never did it. I just thought I might.
我从没抽过，只想试一试
What's new in sex?
所以…最新性事是什么？
最新性事是什么？
The only man I've been with is your father.
我只跟你老爸做过那件事而已
I'm dicing. I'm dicing. I don't hear anything.
我切我切切切，我啥也没听到
This is no offense to your dad, but I was thinking...
我不是在批评你爸爸，亲爱的 我只是在想…
...there might be more.
…或许不只是那样而已
You know what? I cannot have this conversation with you.
对不起，你知道吗？ 我没有办法跟你谈这件事
All right.
好啊…
You come here and drop this bomb on me before you even tell Daddy.
你甚至还没告诉爸 就到我这里来丢这颗炸弹
Do you want my blessing? Want me to talk you out of it?
怎么样？你到底要什么？ 要我的祝福，是不是？
Then what do you want?
那你要我说服你别这样吗？
I guess I figured you would understand.
我猜我以为 在所有人当中你最了解我
Why on earth would I understand this?
为什么我应该要最了解你呢？
You didn't marry your Barry,honey.
你没有嫁给你的贝利
But I married mine.
但是我嫁了我的贝利
We're in trouble. We've only got 12 hours and 36 minutes left.
好了，各位，我们来不及了 我们只剩下12小时又36分
Move,move,move!
快…
I feel like you should have German subtitles.
摩妮卡，我觉得 你应该加上德文字幕才对
Joey,speed it up!
乔伊，快一点嘛
I'm sorry! It's the pigs! They're reluctant to get in the blanket!
抱歉，是猪啦 它们不愿意进毯子啊
How did this happen? I thought you had this planned out.
摩妮卡，怎么会这样呢？ 我以为你全部都计划好了
Do you want me to cry?
你要我哭吗？
Is that what you want?
那就是你要的吗？
Do you wanna see me cry?
你要看到我哭吗？
Sir,no,sir!
长官，不要，长官
All right,you!
好了，你
No. Look,I told you, I am not a part of this thing.
不，我说过我不参与这件事
Look,Ross. I know you have issues with Carol and Susan,and I feel for you.
我知道你跟凯洛和苏珊有过节 我很同情你，真的
But if you don't help, I'm gonna take those hot dogs...
但是如果你不帮我 我会用一堆热狗…
...and create an appetizer called "Pigs In Ross."
…创造出一道 新的开胃菜叫“罗斯猪肉卷”
All right,ball a melon!
好，挖香瓜球
How come I'm stuck dicing when he gets to ball a melon?
为什么我得切丁 他却可以挖香瓜球呢？
-How's it going? -Great! Right on schedule.
进行得怎么样？ 非常顺利，全按时间来
Got my little happy helpers.
有我快乐的小帮手们 是啊
That's fine. Whatever.
很好啊
What's wrong?
怎么了？
Nothing.
没事
Okay,everything. I think we're calling off the wedding.
好吧，有什么 我想我们婚礼要取消了
You're still gonna pay me,right?
你还是会付我钱的吧？
Or something a little less selfish.
或是做不那么自私的事
What's the matter? What happened?
凯洛，发生什么事了？
My parents called to say they weren't coming.
我爸妈今天下午来电话 说他们不来了
I knew they were having trouble with this,but...
我是说 我知道他们不赞成这件事…
...they're my parents. They're supposed to give me away.
…可是他们是我父母啊 他们应该把我嫁出去的
Susan and I fought because I said maybe we should call it off.
然后我跟苏珊大吵了一架 因为我说或许应该取消婚礼
She said,"This isn't for them. It's for us."
然后她说“这不是为了他们 这是为了我们”
And if I couldn't see that, we should cancel the wedding.
“如果我不了解这个的话 或许我们真应该取消婚礼”
I don't know what to do.
我不知道该怎么办
I can't believe I'm gonna say this, but I think Susan's right.
不相信我要这么说 但我认为苏珊是对的
You do?
真的？
Do you love her? And don't be too emphatic about this.
你爱她吗？ 你不用说得太斩钉截铁
Of course I do.
我当然爱她了
Well then,that's it.
那就是了
If George and Adelaide can't accept that,then the hell with them.
如果你的父母无法接受的话 那就去他们的
If my parents didn't want me to marry you...
听着，我是说 若我的父母不要我娶你的话…
... no way that would've stopped me.
…那绝对阻止不了我
Look,this is your wedding.
这是你的婚礼
Do it.
去做
You're right. Of course you're right.
说得对，当然你是对的
So we're back on?
那我们继续吗？
We're back on.
我们继续吧
You heard the woman! Peel! Chop! Devil!
你们听到了，削皮，剁，切
Can't believe I lost two minutes!
真不敢相信我停了两分钟
It just seems so futile.
我真的觉得好白费心机
You know? All these women,and nothing!
你看，这么多女人跟没有一样
I feel like Superman without my powers,you know?
我觉得自己像没了神力的超人
I have the cape, and yet I cannot fly.
我有披风，但我飞不起来
Well,now you understand how I feel every single day.
现在你应该知道 我每天的感觉了吧
The world is my lesbian wedding.
世界是我的同性恋婚礼
Butterscotch?
奶油糖？
No one?
有人要吃吗？
All right, you'll be sorry later.
好吧，待会儿你们会后悔的
-Thank you. -Anytime.
谢谢 随时候教
Ross.
罗斯
Nothing makes God happier...
没有任何一件事…亲朋，好友
...than when two people,any two people, come together in love.
…比两个人 因爱而结合使神更快乐
Friends,family, we're gathered here today...
我们今日齐聚一堂…
...to join Carol and Susan in holy matrimony.
…见证凯洛和苏珊神圣的婚礼
Oh,my God!
老天
Now I've seen everything!
现在我全看见了
She's gone!
她走了
她…她走了
She's gone.
她走了
Go ahead,get married. Go,go!
来吧，结婚啊
Strangers in the night
黑夜中的陌生人
Exchanging glances
目光交会
Wondering in the night
在黑夜中游荡
Would you look at them?
你看看她们
Yeah. Can't help but.
是啊，忍不住…
How's that pig-in-the-blanket working out for you?
那道猪肉卷好不好吃啊？
I wrapped those bad boys.
对，是在下做的耶
I miss Rose.
我想念罗玫
Oh,yeah?
是吗？
I know it's kind of weird,but she was a big part of my life....
我知道这有点怪怪的 但是她是我生活的一部分…
I don't know,I feel alone.
我只是觉得有点孤单
You know,I couldn't help overhearing what you just said.
我听到你刚说的话
I think it's time you forget about Rose, move on with your life.
我想你也该把罗玫抛在脑后了 继续你的生活
How about we get you a drink?
我们去拿杯饮料如何？
Okay. So nice!
好的，你真好
I shouldn't even bother coming up with a line,right?
我连搭讪的话都不用费心了 是不是？
Hey,Mom,having fun?
妈，好玩吗？
Am l! I just danced with a wonderfully large woman.
才好玩呢，我刚才跟一个 好高大的女人跳舞
And three other girls made eyes at me over at the buffet.
另外有三个女孩 在餐点那边对我眨眼睛
I'm not saying it's something I wanna pursue...
我不是说这是我所要追求的…
... but it's nice to know I have options.
…但是知道有选择好令人欣慰
There's more alcohol,right?
还有酒，对吧？
How you doing?
你好吗？
You did a good thing today.
你今天做了件好事
You wanna dance?
想跳舞吗？
No,that's fine.
不，算了
Come on.
来嘛
I'll let you lead.
我让你带舞
Look,penis,schmenis!
谁在乎“老二”
Okay? We're all people.
我们都是人
Which one of us is gonna be the first one to get married?
你们想 我们之中哪一个会先结婚？
Mon,I was married.
摩妮卡，我已经结过婚了
-Yeah,me too,technically. -I had a wedding.
我也是，技术上 我有过婚礼
Just trying to start a discussion.
好啊 只是想开始个有趣的讨论
Which one do you think will be the last to get married?
我想到了 哪一个会最晚结婚？
Isn't Ben in this?
你们说小班算不算？
Of course!
算哪
Absolutely.
当然算了